[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Well, that's it.
I've gone and killed two guys.
All my life, I've wanted to kill
people just by pressing a button.
And now that I've done it,
it's... just... not what
I was hoping for.
How am I going to get out of here now?
Oh, sweet, a service ladder.
Seems like stairs would've made
more sense but that's not my problem,
for I am the climbing master.
Hey, that's the problem:
I didn't KNOW I was killing
anybody; it was manslaughter.
I should've--whoa-ho-ho!
Better not look down.
"Manslaughter" sounds
worse than "murder",
like I'm a butcher in some evil meat shop
and ground up a bunch of people to--
[gunshots, zombie squealing]
Uh-oh! Gunshots! Somebody's going postal.
I knew this would happen.
Wait, that's not... what is that?
Maybe I should be more like this guy.
If he doesn't know what something is,
he just shoots it dead.
GUARD: Gordon! Man am I glad to
see you! What the hell are these things?
GUARD: And why are they
GUARD: wearing Science Team uniforms?
Whoa! Quick draw!
YEAH! SHOOT IT!
HELL YEAH!
That was bad ass. I can
see why you took this job.
Still, what is going on?!
Is this guy contagious?
I'm getting out of here.
I hope I'm not infected.
I'll never get a date if I end
up looking like those guys.
Oh boy! Another body.
Y'know, normally following a
trail of bodies covered in blood
is a sign you're going the WRONG way.
[singing]
Follow the dead body road.
Follow, fol--
Damn! Look at all that blood.
That must be a few hundred dollars'
worth if you were to donate all that.
I wonder if the organs are still good.
I could make a fortune selling
them from all these dead guys.
I guess I could still sell the cadavers if
I could move them before the cops arrive.
Nah, they'd probably just
try to arrest me again.
Oh no! It's the ghosts of those
two guys coming back to haunt me!
Oh, wait. They're just monsters.
Uh...what do I do?
Oh, I know. I'll stand still. They'll pass by
me because they don't have any eyes.
AAAH!
Dammit! How did they see me?
That is so unfair! They don't
have any eyes!
This place bites. I'm going to
find another job.
Oh good! More blood!
I was starting to get worried!
God, what happened?
This guy looks like he got hit
by a steamroller.
[explosion]
Gah!
Why did THAT blow up?
Did we wire this place to
self-destruct or something?
I guess we don't have enough
dead people here yet.
I've got to get out of here.
[panel buzzes]
Oh, you've gotta be shitting me...
I'm going to sue the HELL out of
Black Mesa when I get out of here!
Locking your workers in?
That's what the
Triangle Shirtwaist Factory did;
locked its workers in, then there
was a fire then everybody died.
That's a formula for success!
DAMMIT!
Wow, we're making history right now!
CRAP HISTORY!
[explosion]
RRRRR!
What?
Ha-hah!
I am incredible.
Is there any end to the number
of problems I can solve
just by beating the
hell out of something?
I'm not sure there is!
Yep! That's how I say "Open sesame":
with a crowbar to the face!
Aw man, the tram's gone.
You're waiting for it too, huh?
Hey, you sure this catwalk's safe?
Hey, why is the guard dead?
You kill him?
[metal groaning]
I want some answers!
Uh-oh.
SCIENTIST: No! Stay back!
SCIENTIST: GORDON!
Oh jeez. Okay, give me your hand!
[scientist screams]
No, your OTHER hand, you idiot!
[distant splat]
Ah, you suck!
Now you're dead and I STILL
can't get out of here!
Thanks for nothing!
Why does everyone have to keep dying on me?
Is it really so hard to just not die?
I mean, look at me.
I was in the chamber at friggin'
Ground Zero and I'm still here!
Yet, you guys slip on
a banana peel and that's it!
Ugh, Darwin was right. I didn't realize
I was working with a bunch of lemmings.
I guess I may as well
check that opening out.
I'll go around so I don't have
to walk in the blood.
Though, honestly, at the rate I'm going,
I'll be knee deep in it
[techno music]
before I get out of here.
At least they turned the volume down.
[techno music plays]
Oh, crap! Another facehugger.
[techno music plays, explosion]
[techno music plays]
Ha ha ha!
Oh, that's just great.
[techno music plays]
My enemy is the enemy of my other enemy.
I wouldn't hate computers so much
[techno music plays]
if they did more useful things like that.
I wonder if the guys in here
[techno music plays]
died from the aliens
[techno music plays, explosions]
or just raved themselves to death.
Okay, place is blowing up,
[techno music plays, explosions]
time to leave.
Escape from techno hell!
Hey, one of the guys is
fighting the facehugger!
C'mon, hit it!
Hit it with a stick!
Aww...
Those things really ARE facehuggers!
I hope they don't bleed acid, too.
I'm glad I watched the movie.
Okay, twitching dead guy
and a strobe light.
That's not creepy at all.
I'm... just... gonna... go...
...yeah...
[gunshots]
Hey-hey. Gunshots.
Where there's a gun, there's fun.
Or not.
Uh-oh.  Uh, you need some help?
Guess not, huh?
Well...
Whoa-ho-ho-ho, what's this?
Your death was not in vain, pal.
I'll shoot everyone in this
building if I have to.
Welp, time to play God.
Let's see people disrespect me now.
They'll find out what happens
when you mess with the Freeman.